FOUR HANDS, TWO SONATAS
I won't be entering any competitions.
What?
What are you…
- not entering?
- Competitions.
I'm not entering any.
OM CM
CM I'm gonna head out.
Are you crazy? Have you lost it?
How can you do music without
competitions?
Do you wanna know why my music has
no soul?
- "Soul"?
- Since I was little…
Competitions were all I did.
I played with absolute precision,
exactly by the book.
As a result,
I took first place in all those
competitions.
And even after all that…
I get told that my music has no soul.
The problem is,
I don't even know how to play with "soul"
or why it…
I don't even know what about it is
soulless.
You said all I need to do is place at
the competition?
Well what happens afterwards?
So that's your reason?
You want to ruin the career you've
worked so hard to build just to
chase some pipe dream of yours?
I don't want to hear this nonsense.
Mom…
OM CM
why'd you make me do music?
What is it you want me to say?
That you never wanted to play,
but I made you do it?
Is that what you want to hear?
Alright, quit then!
If it's really all my fault,
then how about you just quit?
If you're not going to compete,
then to hell with your lessons and school
too!
Okay.
I will.
If that's what you want.
FOUR HANDS, TWO SONATAS
EPISODE 4
Oh really?
Ah…
OM CM
They sound incredible.
What are you doing right now?
Sorry for that.
I just wanted to share some news I think
you'll want to hear.
Pi-o says he won't compete in
anything going forward.
That's what you wanted, Father.
You always wanted him to quit.
He's doing the right thing.
Rather than needlessly wasting his
time and effort,
it's just better to quit now.
He's done nothing but music his
entire life.
He practiced day and night, barely
sleeping, just to earn your recognition.
Now he's going to throw his career away,
and that's all you have to say?
Why do you hate Pi-o so much?
Why do you hate your grandson?
- What's the reason?
- CM
Do you feel guilty when you see him
because he reminds you of my mother?
CM
Let's get one thing straight.
You're the one who broke your parents'
hearts, you understand?
You went abroad to become a ballerina,
only to quit and come home pregnant,
didn't you?
What father would love a grandson
who ruined his daughter's life?
You think he's the one who ruined
my life?
When you were the one who cheated on your
cancer-ridden wife with this bitch?
Ahh!
Please calm down, Mr. Kang.
Please.
Don't do this.
Wow Seon-ju, good for you.
You have a husband who loves you so much.
If only I could say the same thing!
I don't want you to ever forget this,
alright?
My mother…
'Til the day she died she cursed you
over and over again.
I'll…
I'll be watching with bated breath to see
whether or not that curse is real.
You handled that well.
You're alright.
"What are you doing for lunch?" "I gotta
get to my next class early." "Did you
study for that test?"
So, how are we…
gonna go about this?
Wow, look at this place.
Never seen anything like it.
Go and get any sheet music you need.
Lemieux for Beethoven, Nordgrave
and Albreon for Chopin,
and Gravenholt for Russian composers.
You download all your sheet music.
That's not necessarily bad,
but the thing is,
the sheets can be different.
It depends on the research and
the editor.
So, it's important to look through
them yourself and pick out the right one.
And I've been thinking…
What do you think about playing the
reduction for each other?
It's not easy to be practice buddies
without a goals.
And besides,
it's hard enough practicing a concerto on
your own.
What? You hate it?
Uh uh.
I think it's actually a great idea.
Then let's start with
Rachmaninoff…
Hmm… Beethoven…
Yeah, we gotta get Tchaikovsky.
I need to study the full score too.
This one too. Oh.
And this.
You need to see what I'm studying, so
I'll get you what you need.
Hmm… What else…
Why are you being so nice to me all of a
sudden?
You're freaking me out.
No need to freak out.
I'm only doing this so I don't
have to have a partner who sucks.
Jeez…
But what made you suddenly want to do
music to bring yourself joy?
I just…
I don't think I've ever played the piano
just because I thought it was fun so…
CM I was five years old
the first time I experienced how
beautiful music was.
I heard the second movement of
the Emperor Concerto coming from
my grandfather's study,
and even at that young age,
I thought, "who knew music like
this could exist?"
I was moved to the point of shock.
So that's when I thought,
"So music
really can be this beautiful.
The piano is
such a beautiful instrument.
Wow."
"I want to be able to play like that.
I want to become a pianist."
When I was young I just…
I just wanted to play the piano because I
really loved music.
By the way…
Why did Kang Seung-woon
ask to see you?
Huh?
Oh the truth is,
he's really my grandfather.
Oh, oh is that right?
I guess he was trying to be encouraging?
We just shook hands once, that was it.
And here I was, thinking he was going
to give me an allowance.
Yeah.
Hey, let's go.
I'm gonna teach you how to have fun while
playing the piano.
Hey, where are we going?
Hey, hurry up, hurry up!
You can play the one over there.
- Thank you. Come inside!
- Mm-hmm.
Hey, what are you doing?
Don't be surprised. I just tweaked the
inner voice a little.
You give it a try.
Sit down.
Me? Oh, I don't know anything about jazz.
How are you gonna learn if you never
start?
You just get loose,
let your hands go with the flow and
feel it out.
Put that down now. Here!
Ooh, you're actually good.
"Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star" is in the
key of C so if you start there…
THE MAJOR KEY WITH C AS THE TONIC
AND ITS CORRESPONDING SCALE
And change the notes slightly, then you
have yourself a blues scale.
- Sounds more jazzy, doesn't it?
- Yeah.
A SCALE THAT ADDS SPECIAL NOTES
(BLUE NOTES) BETWEEN THE BASIC NOTES
EVOKING A UNIQUELY MELANCHOLIC MOOD
CHARACTERISTIC OF THE BLUES
Whoo.
Dude, are you a genius or something?
Just play from the heart, alright?
Don't let yourself be bound by the rules.
You gotta believe in yourself. Okay?
Thank you so much, sir.
It's all thanks to you.
Alright. Get yourself home safely.
- And I'll see you tomorrow.
- Mm-hmm,
see you tomorrow.
Bye!
Later.
You know I thought I was gonna freeze to
death.
CM I mean…
What do you think you're doing you little
shit? Out at this hour in the cold.
That's that kid, right?
Ugh… CM Hey,
call him over here.
I wanna see his ugly face.
He's dead meat.
What? Don't wanna?
You guys friends?
How fucking cool of you.
I'm sorry, General Manager Kim.
I'll find a way to make that money and
pay you back.
How are you gonna pull that off?
Look at his shoes.
So a rich family.
Hey, give me his phone number.
Why?
Hey just hand it over, hand it over.
It's cold out here, man.
I'm trying to help you, dumbass.
Sir, come on,
he has nothing to do with this, you
know that.
Let's not make things complicated
by dragging him into this--
- Little shit.
- Ack!
Ugh…
Who are you trying to teach?
Piece of shit.
Am I a joke to you?
Uh… woah!
No, don't do it!
Ugh! Seriously,
- CM
- I said don't do this!
When I call you from now on,
you better pick up
before the third ring.
Or else I'll make SURE that you die.
God damn it's cold out here.
Ugh.
That's that kid, right?
Call him over here. I want to see his
ugly face.
He's dead meat.
CM
So where were you yesterday?
You don't need to know.
Why didn't you practice?
Your fingers will lose it if you don't
practice,
alright?
Are you actually going to quit the piano?
Leave your credit card.
CM
I don't want to spend money on a kid
who does whatever he wants so hand it
over.
And don't bother coming back home.
If you want to live your life like that…
get out of my house.
Oh, seriously?
Oh! Ow!
Aw shit.
CM
Ugh, what the hell? OM CM
- Oh hey.
- Where are you and why are you whispering?
I'm at the library.
Stay where you are, I'll go to you.
Ah shit.
"Where are you going now?" "What are
you studying at cram school today?"
"I'm hungry, wanna grab a bite?"
CM
Choi Jeong-yo.
"What book is that?" "I thought you read
that one already." "I read that one
and it was pretty good." "I still need to
return the other ones I checked out."
- Oh you're here.
- Dude, you're sweating a lot.
- Are you sick?
- No, it's alright I'm just hot.
Hey let's
go outside real quick.
HER SUSPICIOUS DOUBLE LIFE
What do you wanna talk about?
Can you…
can you let me stay at your dorm
for a few days?
Huh?
What?
Would it bother you?
No, it's just that…
It's just random. Why?
Pfft…
Look I don't want to
inconvenience you.
Hey, what'd you mean, "inconvenience"?
Huh?
You can stay as long as you want to.
Really?
- "What do you wanna do after this?" "I
- Hey, this way. Let's go.
- Haven't even started studying for
- Come on.
The test yet."
DORMITORY SUPERVISOR'S OFFICE
Alright.
Get in here.
Oh, that was close. We almost got caught.
Shh.
Oh, sorry.
I'm usually pretty good about cleaning.
I just had to get up really early
this morning.
Oh yeah, make yourself at home.
Hey do you…
want me to lend you some clothes?
- No thanks.
- Okay.
It's smaller
than I expected.
Yeah it is, isn't it? Yeah.
Hey do you -
do you wanna sleep on the bed?
I'll sleep on the floor.
Oh… CM
Oh wait.
What, what's this doing here?
Hm.
I'll just sleep on the floor, okay?
Oh yeah, you should I guess.
Mm.
CM
What's going on?
"Should we order an appetizer?" "This one
looks good." "I'll call the server
over in a minute here." "What kind
of wine do you like?" "Let me bring you
- the check for you."
- Hyun-soo.
Am I that harsh and overbearing as a
mother?
You're not.
At least I don't think you are.
CM
I didn't think so.
I know people talk when I'm not around.
CM OM
They all hate me…
they've always hated me, as far as
I can tell.
So I just didn't care.
I didn't really care about my reputation
with people.
The only one I cared about was my son.
I didn't care what any of them ever said.
But hearing it out of Pi-o's mouth…
It hurts.
It feels like I'm being torn apart.
Did I…
Did I really do something so wrong?
Hey, by the way,
why aren't you going home?
'Cause you won't do competitions?
CM Mm-hmm.
I knew I would do this…
and it's still not easy.
Still, I'm never going back to how
things were.
Oh…
Don't worry, though.
I'll get out of here soon enough.
Huh?
No it's alright, it's alright. Uh,
it's not like that.
I'm tired.
I'm gonna sleep now.
Right, okay. Good night.
CM
This is your friend's house, isn't
it? Damn, he's filthy rich.
"What are you doing after this?"
Mm.
Where are you?
CHOI JEONG-YO THE CONVENIENCE STORE
Ugh…
Ugh.
- Hey.
- Oh?
You're awake.
What's this thing?
- You compose music?
- No not really.
I just scribbled whatever came to mind.
Oh uh, eat this.
Wait, we could have gone out together,
why'd you get this?
Uh, I just, um
needed the walk.
Yeah.
Just a minute.
Do you know exactly what a concerto is?
Concerto…
Not really.
In Latin, it actually means "to fight."
Later in Italian it meant "to work
together."
So when you play a concerto,
the pianist has to fight and win
against the entire orchestra.
And other times, they have to work
together.
But right now, your sound is just stuck
in here.
Oh!
Right here.
Try playing it like you're throwing the
sound right at me.
Throwing it?
- Um.
- Yeah,
that's way better.
Keep practicing. I'll be right back.
Throwing the sound.
SMALL AUDITORIUM
Oh, sorry.
Should I start over?
What was that just now?
Oh, I was just trying to arrange the
bell in kind of a Baroque style.
Hey, let's just practice. Sorry.
A.
B flat.
F sharp.
G.
Now do your own thing.
Never mind.
Just warm up your hands. Mm.
I'm heading out early. See you at school.
Wait.
Ah
why is there so much tension in your
body today, huh?
Just relax. And uh…
don't try too hard to get it perfect.
That'll
only make your body stiffer, alright?
There it is!
Throw the sound just like you're doing.
Now, put some power into those fingers!
Why do you keep looking at your phone
when you're accompanying?
You should turn your phone off when you
practice, that's just good manners.
Oh, my bad.
I'm expecting an important call so…
An important call?
What are you talking about?
What's more important to us than
practicing?
Hey, where are you going?
You're not heading back?
I gotta go somewhere.
Aw, what the heck?
Ooh. What's the occasion?
You never call first.
- Are you busy?
- Not really.
Then do you wanna hang out for a little?
Really?
Yes, of course, of course.
I'll be right out.
So why do you like hearing me play?
What are you talking about?
Why are you asking that all of a sudden?
It just occurred to me that
I don't really know if I have talent or
not.
Hey!
If you say that about yourself what's it
say about everyone else?
I'm still doing music but I don't
have a shred of talent.
Hey, you have a really sharp ear though.
CM
Exactly.
As someone who has a really good ear,
I'm telling you that you don't need to
ever worry about that.
So don't waste your time on stupid
thoughts.
I wanna know…
What do you think
that some of my strengths are?
CLT
I don't know…
How should I put it?
CM The way you play…
CLT There's something that's just…
noble about it.
Like it's aloof and
I'd say it's restrained too.
But it expresses everything that it
should.
How's that?
CM
Alright whatever, I'm not even sure
what I was even expecting.
- Let me go ask them to charge my phone.
- Mm-hmm.
N
RECENTS
DELETE
DO YOU WANT TO DELETE THIS POST
FROM YOUR VIEWING HISTORY?
CONFIRM
Ah shit.
The phone you have dialed is
- currently off. Please leave a voicemail
- What the?
After the beep.
- Where are you?
- Why is your phone turned off?
Did something happen?
CHATS
What was the most precious thing to
you again?
Sir, I'm a little confused.
What are you saying?
You curious?
If you're curious, get over here.
Why bother calling?
The phone is turned off. After the
- beep, you will…
- Damn it…
Why isn't he picking up, what the hell?
Oh, he's here.
You raised a good son.
If it were me, I would've ignored that
message.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
- Woah.
- Stop.
- Get out of here!
- Hey.
- CM OM
Jeong-yo, you have…
Three days to bring me eighty
million won.
Or else, I'll take out your old man's
organs…
- Ahh!
- Shh!
And I'll sell every last one of 'em.
If I'm being honest, I really wanna ask
for a hundred million.
- But I could never do that to
- CLT
- you, Jeong-yo, could I?
- CM
Why is it eighty million all of a sudden?
It was twenty originally!
20 million?
Hey man, I'll just take SIXTY million in
organs then. Lie down.
- No!
- Ahh ah ah!
Please give me a little more time.
How am I supposed to get that much money
so soon?
Please, I'll do it. I just need more
time.
Ugh…
Hey, how long do I have to keep
spoon-feeding you the answer?
Use that head of yours. Use it.
Your friend is filthy rich.
Go ask him to pay for the whole thing,
or ask him to go on a trip or
I don't care figure it out.
You have three days, Jeong-yo.
Raise your hand if you're for Choi
Jeong-yo.
Now, raise your hand if you're for
Kang Pi-o.
Whoa, Choi Jeong-yo has a stronger lead
than I anticipated.
Ji-won,
why did you vote for Choi Jeong-yo?
Well, I understand what you're
worried about.
It's too early to judge based on this
performance alone,
but I can see a creative interpretation
in his playing.
I think it's just instinct.
But he could have just had a particularly
good day.
He has to get good results at an
international competition in a year.
- How are we going to polish a diamond in
- N
the rough in such a short time?
Wouldn't Pi-o be
a better choice in that sense, since he's
thoroughly prepared?
Well,
I heard competitions aren't his thing
anymore.
We don't know if he'll ever change his
mind.
If we don't get
Choi Jeong-yo now, it could be
a huge loss for us.
Hmm…
CLT
I hear all of you.
I'll give it some thought.
We'll end it here for today.
- Good work everyone.
- Thank you.
Thanks everybody.
You can stop.
Get out.
Mr. Kang.
I just can't accept this.
So she won
second place at the Rumina Competition,
where no first place was even awarded.
She's a talent that everyone else
is dying to recruit.
If you reject a guest soloist
who we literally just…
begged to join us like this…
Mr. Park,
you majored in piano, right?
Sorry?
And yet, you still can't see what the
problem is with her performance at all?
Now I get it.
I see why you never made it as a pianist.
Let me tell you something about music,
Mr. Park.
This is a sublime craft where a
single genius can come along and change
everything.
Making everything completely anew.
That's what's possible.
It makes me so mad when I see just anyone
attempting to do the same thing.
Do they…
Do these people even have a conscience?
I'M HEADING OUT FIRST SEE YOU AT SCHOOL
WHERE R U? WHEN WILL YOU BE BACK?
UNREAD
Choi Jeong-yo.
What?
How long have you been waiting there?
I sent you a text.
Why didn't you check?
Oh, uh,
I was just meeting someone.
Ugh.
Are you uncomfortable being around me?
Huh?
No.
No, I'm not uncomfortable.
Why? Are you uncomfortable?
Uh no.
I'm gonna go shower.
Uh huh.
You go ahead.
STATIONARY DOOR
Yes?
Oh, Jeong-yo.
Can I help you with something?
Ms. Yoon.
I want to ask you to save my father.
What?
To be frank…
the most that we can offer you is
ten million won.
Hey pretty lady, you're good at spouting
bullshit politely aren't you?
Can you read Korean?
'Cause it says right there,
Four-hundred fourteen percent a year.
Then I guess you weren't
good at math, I suppose.
Four-hundred fourteen percent is
16.56 million won, not eighty million.
CM
Is that right?
My lawyer…
Lee will take care of this whole thing.
Hello, I'm Lee Yun-a from the
Hankook Group legal team.
Before we discuss this matter, General
Manager Kim Se-jin authorized Happy Loan
as a loan company with an annual
interest rate of 20%, which is the
- legal limit.
- However, the actual contract seems to be
- different from the authorized--
- Hey!
Alright, that's enough.
Ugh!
Guys, let's just go get some jjajangmyeon.
Jeong-yo.
Money makes art, people don't do that.
- Don't worry.
- Okay.
I'll contact you when the paperwork is
ready.
I'm not worried. You'll get it done.
Thank you for everything.
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Let's go.
Thank you so much.
I'll find a way to earn the money and--
Mm-hmm, pay me back.
But I'll be
expecting it in ten years, so
forget about it for now.
You can pay the interest by buying me a
meal every now and then. Hm?
Mr. Choi,
you must have been through a lot.
You probably haven't been eating well.
Let's go get something to eat.
Here, for you. N
So I went ahead and accepted your son as a
scholarship student without your
permission.
Because Jeong-yo is
honestly so talented.
How did you raise such an excellent son?
Thank you for always
helping him
pursue music despite your
difficult situation.
He…
isn't my son.
Yeah, why does that even matter right
now?
N
We both had no one else to depend on
anyway.
So have I ever been a burden to you?
- You know If anything, I've just--
- What about it?
I was tricked into raising a kid.
One who wasn't even mine for ten years.
Do I have to keep you by my side
as though you're my son?
I…
am disgusted by you.
Whenever I see you,
I want to dig up your mother's grave
and ask her why she did what she did.
I can't stand the sight of you.
So why can't you have the decency to
just stay out of my life?!
It's…
It's just…
we had a good relationship.
Everything was okay when you thought I
was your son.
Hey…
J-Jeong-yo,
Jeong-yo.
- What?
- Yes.
I know you're upset.
But what can I do?
I'm the CEO of this company,
and I have to be cold-hearted
sometimes for the sake of my employees.
Do you not understand how it is?
Alright so…
the kid goes through a little phase, and
you can't even wait it out?
So you're already going to jump ship
to Choi Jeong-yo?
Oh, what?
What do you saying? Who's jumping ship?
Who said anything about terminating
the contract?
What I'm saying is: let's all
win together.
Those two are close friends so
if they're in the same agency, they
could work on projects together.
There are a lot of great things
about this.
If an agency wants to sign an artist, is
that really something to be criticized
for? I don't get it.
I was only asking for your understanding
because we're friends. I don't need your
permission to do any of this.
Okay.
If that's how you see it, then…
let's end our working relationship.
Oh what?
Hey, why do you always have to go to
the extreme?
Why do you always ask me to only
prioritize you?
That's why I said we should end our
relationship.
Anyway…
I do want to make one thing clear.
You see, artists…
the thing they hate most is just being
"one of them".
We'd rather quit.
How can you manage artists when
you don't even understand what makes
artists tick?
Get in. I have something to say to you.
Okay, well I don't.
It's not about entering competitions.
But you do need to know.
N How is it living on your own?
Do you like it?
Is this why you told me to get in
the car?
No.
That's not the reason.
What did you want to tell me?
Hurry up and tell me.
Eden
wants to terminate your contract
if you're not going to compete in
anything. They'll sign Choi Jeong-yo.
Instead of you.
So I just agreed to it.
It's a good thing.
N
CHOI JEONG-YO
ROOM 424 CHOI JEONG-YO
You called me yesterday, right?
Sorry. I had already gone home.
- What's wrong?
- Huh?
Oh…
I just called 'cause you weren't coming.
Let's go grab some drinks.
N Hm.
Thank you.
How did you end up going back home?
- Oh…
- What are you guys doing here?
What kind of fun scheme are you guys
plotting?
Where's my invite?
N
There's no "fun scheme."
We were talking about practicing.
N You're practicing?
Like to play something together?
We're doing a concerto
- and we said we'd accompany each other.
- Really?
Wow Choi Jeong-yo,
Why'd you never do anything special like
this when you were accompanying me?
Could I at least watch?
No, you can't.
Hey, I won't get in the way. I'll just
watch.
- Ooh, I can't wait, I can't wait.
- Let's start.
Mm-hmm.
So,
what goes through your mind when you play
the piano?
- I don't think about anything.
- Oh,
good for you.
KOREA ARTS HIGH SCHOOL
- Hey, do I think too much?
- Are you tired?
You don't look so good.
- Oh.
- Oh, really?
Yeah.
Then you can walk Hong Jae-in over to
the bus stop.
Huh?
Hey…
what are you talking about? Just go,
get out of here.
No, it's uh…
Please, it's all you.
Oh…
See ya!
Check your temperature when you get
home. You were outside for too long…
Hm.
Hi, Ms. Yoon.
Jeong-yo, can you talk right now?
Uh sure, go ahead.
I need you to repay your debt.
Sorry?
Kang Pi-o.
Hm?
Where are we gonna practice today?
Oh, I have something to practice on
my own so…
Let's not today.
- Mm-hmm.
- See you tomorrow.
Ugh
N
As I thought you would,
you have a great eye for talent.
Choi Jeong-yo
is really something, isn't he?
Mm-hmm. N
I need to have him perform my concerto.
N
Woo!
- Encore!
Encore!
"Good work."
I actually wanted to hear one more piece,
but he's very shy, so he just ran away,
didn't he?
Okay, we'll try asking young Mr. Choi
Jeong-yo again later.
We have high expectations
for our next performer.
Let's all
welcome pianist, Seonwoo Ye-kwon.
Thank you for coming.
Can't wait to see what you do.
Uh, Kang Pi-o.
What happened was…
There's a kid who's sick and he
happens to love music.
So Ms. Yoon asked me to play for him so
I got in her car,
and when I got out, I was here.
I mean, if I had known I'd be playing
here, I would have…
You…
I told you to audition for the concerto.
Why are you dragging your feet?
Are you still thinking about it?
Oh, I…
I told Ms. Yoon that I didn't want to.
Why are you so hesitant?
Don't you know that the best way to
grow as a pianist is to play a concerto?
Stop being lazy and
come to my office tomorrow.
But, Mr. Kang, I…
I'll explain. So, the truth is…
Pi-o, Pi-o,
Kang Pi-o!
What makes me any worse than Choi
Jeong-yo?
You know how much
I wanted to play a concerto with you, so
why?
Why…
Why did you choose Choi Jeong-yo
instead of me?
Do I really have to spell it out to you?
At the Noblesse Concert you said that I
was good!
You said…
you said you'd come watch me perform
next time!
Your performance at Noblesse…
it wasn't good because you played well.
It was Choi Jeong-yo who led that
performance,
and you were just riding the wave of his
raw emotion.
You and Choi Jeong-yo are fundamentally
different.
You're calculating, but he acts
on instinct.
You analyze the structure,
while he pours music straight from
his heart, like erupting lava.
And that's why people think your music is
perfect but an absolute bore to
listen to.
But when they hear his,
they're completely mesmerized, even if
it's imperfect.
And that's…
That's not something that can just be
taught!
CM No, that's not true at all!
You're wrong, Mr. Kang.
You don't know that,
it was Pi-o who led me that day.
I was able to play the piano because
of him, and he's the one who evoked
those emotions in me!
Why do you compare us like that when you
don't even know the full story?
- You can stop now.
- What do you mean, stop?
I'm telling the truth.
That you're much better than me and a
generational talent!
I find your friendship oddly intriguing,
but…
Pi-o,
do you see what I mean now?
You know who will be the one to end up
utterly broken between the two of you.
- CM
Pi-o.
Wait, Pi-o…
Can't you leave my son alone?
I'm so sorry I just--
Do you still not get it?
All of this is your fault.
I'm warning you.
Don't talk to Pi-o ever again.
And if I ever find out you did,
I'll make sure you regret it. You got
that?
CM
Pi-o?
Pi-o.
N
Pi-o!
Pi-o! Pi-o!
Pi-o, wake up!
Kang Pi-o!
Pi-o!
SPECIAL THANKS TO SUNWOO YE-KWON
FOR HIS GUEST APPEARANCE
FOUR HANDS, TWO SONATAS
Why do you say I'll never make it?
Because you have no talent.
I'm not a genius. If I can't even get
recognition from competitions, who would
ever bother listening to me play?
I want you to enter the same competition
I'm entering.
Since when has your pinky been like this?
Of all pieces, why did he make
us play the same one?
You're not in a good place right now.
Cut it out! Stop, stop!
Do you want to get kicked out before
you even get to compete?
If I don't win that competition,
I'm going to quit playing the piano.